<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>

  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="HumanResources.UpdateFeatureBase">
    <modNameReadable>Human Resources</modNameReadable>
    <modIdentifier>JPT_HumanResources</modIdentifier>
    <linkUrl>https://ko-fi.com/jptrrs</linkUrl>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="HumanResources.UpdateFeatureBase">
	<defName>HumanResources_0_1</defName>
	<assemblyVersion>0.1</assemblyVersion>
	<content>
&lt;b&gt;You've been recruited to test this out!&lt;/b&gt;
|This is a work in progress, and we're thrilled you are giving it a shot! Bear in mind you might encounter some errors and incompatibilities. If you do, please let me know. Don't forget to hit Ctrl+F12 to upload the error log and send me that link. I'm also open to any suggestions you might have, so please keep in touch!
|
|&lt;b&gt;Here's a quick guide to get you started:&lt;/b&gt;
|img:TechButton
|Check out the new tab for your colonists. It displays the sum of their knowledge, and that represents the limit of what they are able to build, repair, craft, grow and also the weapons they are able to equip. A starting knowledge set is generated for every pawn based on background, age and faction. From there, its your task to educate them!
|
|img:Study+Shelf
|Build a &lt;i&gt;study desk&lt;/i&gt; and a &lt;i&gt;bookshelf&lt;/i&gt; as soon as you can. This allows your colonists to &lt;i&gt;document&lt;/i&gt; their knowledge into books and then &lt;i&gt;study&lt;/i&gt; books to acquire new knowledge (when assigned to &lt;i&gt;study&lt;/i&gt;). 
|
|img:ResearchBenches
|These are the new research benches. Now they operate like the other work stations: you'll need to assign bills for your colonists to perform research. And what they learn will remain only in their heads until they can write a book on their discoveries. Only when that book is archived on a bookshelf you will really have unlocked that technology.
|
|img:Target+Dummy
|When you discover new weapons, your colonists will need to train at these facilities in order to learn how to use them (for that, they must also be assigned to &lt;i&gt;study&lt;/i&gt;). The &lt;i&gt;training dummy&lt;/i&gt; is for meleee weapons and the &lt;i&gt;target stand&lt;/i&gt; is for ranged ones. You can also task them with &lt;i&gt;practicing&lt;/i&gt; a weapon. This will allow them to sharpen their melee or shooting skills!
|
|img:Quarantine|caption:&lt;b&gt;Please, consider supporting the making of this mod!&lt;/b&gt; 
This is being made as I try to mantain myself as isolated as possible during the COVID-19 crisis. Like many people around the world, my living has been impacted by the global efforts to contain the pandemic, and this is my effort to remain productive. If you are able to contribute, you can buy me a coffee on https://ko-fi.com/jptrrs, or follow the link above. 
Many, many thanks for your support!
    </content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
  
  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="HumanResources.UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>HumanResources_0_11</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>0.11</assemblyVersion>
    <content>
      &lt;b&gt;Friendly Update (IMPORTANT!)&lt;/b&gt;
      |The feedback you gave us on this first testing round has provided very valuable insights on how to improve &lt;i&gt;Human Resources&lt;/i&gt;. Beyond the usual fixes and compatibility patches, this update adresses some issues to try and make it more intuitive and give you the player better information. These are the main changes. If you're in the middle of a game you started before the update, there are some changes you should be aware of. (Also, in that case, if you get any errors, please try deleting any current bills on research and study benches.)
      |1. The &lt;i&gt;Learn&lt;/i&gt; work type has been renamed to &lt;b&gt;Study&lt;/b&gt;.
      |2. The &lt;i&gt;document technology&lt;/i&gt; task you assign your colonists to write books down now also belongs to the &lt;b&gt;study&lt;/b&gt; work type, since that's made at the &lt;i&gt;study desk&lt;/i&gt;. ;-)
      |3. It used to be possible for a pawn to learn a new weapon only if the corresponding technology book was already stored in one of your bookshelves. &lt;b&gt;Now, if the pawn already knows that technolgy personally, he or she will also be able to train with that weapon&lt;/b&gt;. To allow for this, the weapons list on the recipe window no longer hides the weapons your colony can't access. Therefore, keep in mind there will be weapons you can check but your pawns won't necessarily be able to learn.
      |4. The &lt;i&gt;Tech tab&lt;/i&gt; has gained some new capabilities. Check the new controls!|img:newButtons
      |5. The speed for the research and study tasks now scales with the difficulty level selected for your game, slowing down on higher levels (on top of the difficulty scaling the base game already applies to the research task). This means researching with &lt;i&gt;Human Resources&lt;/i&gt; will be even more difficult on higher difficulty levels. You can turn that off, if you wish, on the mod options menu.
      |Check the full change notes on our Steam page.
      |
      |&lt;b&gt;Please, consider supporting the making of this mod!&lt;/b&gt; If you are able to contribute, you can buy me a coffee on https://ko-fi.com/jptrrs, or follow the link above. Many, many thanks!
    </content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
  
  <!--<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="HumanResources.UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>HumanResources_0_16</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>0.16</assemblyVersion>
    <content>
      &lt;b&gt;Refactoring Update (IMPORTANT!)&lt;/b&gt;
      |The feedback you gave us on this first testing round has provided very valuable insights on how to improve &lt;i&gt;Human Resources&lt;/i&gt;. Beyond the usual fixes and compatibility patches, this update adresses some issues to try and make it more intuitive and give you the player better information. These are the main changes. If you're in the middle of a game you started before the update, there are some changes you should be aware of. (Also, in that case, if you get any errors, please try deleting any current bills on research and study benches.)
      |1. The &lt;i&gt;Learn&lt;/i&gt; work type has been renamed to &lt;b&gt;Study&lt;/b&gt;.
      |2. The &lt;i&gt;document technology&lt;/i&gt; task you assign your colonists to write books down now also belongs to the &lt;b&gt;study&lt;/b&gt; work type, since that's made at the &lt;i&gt;study desk&lt;/i&gt;. ;-)
      |3. It used to be possible for a pawn to learn a new weapon only if the corresponding technology book was already stored in one of your bookshelves. &lt;b&gt;Now, if the pawn already knows that technolgy personally, he or she will also be able to train with that weapon&lt;/b&gt;. To allow for this, the weapons list on the recipe window no longer hides the weapons your colony can't access. Therefore, keep in mind there will be weapons you can check but your pawns won't necessarily be able to learn.
      |4. The &lt;i&gt;Tech tab&lt;/i&gt; has gained some new capabilities. Check the new controls!|img:newButtons
      |5. The speed for the research and study tasks now scales with the difficulty level selected for your game, slowing down on higher levels (on top of the difficulty scaling the base game already applies to the research task). This means researching with &lt;i&gt;Human Resources&lt;/i&gt; will be even more difficult on higher difficulty levels. You can turn that off, if you wish, on the mod options menu.
      |Check the full change notes on our Steam page.
      |
      |&lt;b&gt;Please, consider supporting the making of this mod!&lt;/b&gt; If you are able to contribute, you can buy me a coffee on https://ko-fi.com/jptrrs, or follow the link above. Many, many thanks!
    </content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>-->
  
</Defs>