<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>

  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="HumanResources.UpdateFeatureBase">
    <modNameReadable>Human Resources</modNameReadable>
    <modIdentifier>JPT_HumanResources</modIdentifier>
    <linkUrl>https://www.patreon.com/jptrrs</linkUrl>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="HumanResources.UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>HumanResources_1_0</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>1.0</assemblyVersion>
    <targetAudience>NewPlayers</targetAudience>
    <content>
      |&lt;b&gt;WELCOME TO HUMAN RESOURCES!&lt;/b&gt;
      |People now only know what they have learned! Here's a quick guide to get you started:
      |
      |img:TechButton
      |Check out the new tab for your colonists. It displays the sum of their knowledge, and that represents the limit of what they are able to build, repair, craft, grow and also the weapons they are able to equip. A starting knowledge set is generated for every pawn based on background, age and faction. From there, its your task to educate them!
      |
      |img:Study+Shelf
      |Build a &lt;i&gt;study desk&lt;/i&gt; and a &lt;i&gt;bookshelf&lt;/i&gt; as soon as you can. This allows your colonists to &lt;i&gt;document&lt;/i&gt; their knowledge into books and then &lt;i&gt;study&lt;/i&gt; books to acquire new knowledge (when assigned to the &lt;i&gt;study&lt;/i&gt; work type).
      |
      |img:HomeworkIndicator,HomeworkOnTree
      |You must assign them study and document tasks individually. You can do that by clicking directly on the desired technologies on their Tech tabs or on the main Research screen, where you can also assign &lt;i&gt;research&lt;/i&gt; tasks.
      |
      |img:ResearchBenches
      |For research, you'll still need research benches, but they have been slimmed down to better fit alongside your library. Keep in mind what your researchers learn remain only in their heads until they can write a book on their discoveries. Only when that book is archived on a bookshelf you will really have unlocked that technology.
      |
      |img:NetworkServer,NetworkTerminal
      |Physical books will only get you so far. To deal with space-age knowledge, you'll need information-age infrastructure. On the late game, get ready to build your very own &lt;i&gt;network server&lt;/i&gt; to host your library and the accompanying &lt;i&gt;network terminal&lt;/i&gt; for uploading and downloading digital knowledge!
      |
      |img:Target+Dummy
      |When you discover new weapons, your colonists will need to train at these facilities in order to learn how to use them (for that, they must also be assigned to &lt;i&gt;study&lt;/i&gt;). The &lt;i&gt;training dummy&lt;/i&gt; is for meleee weapons and the &lt;i&gt;target stand&lt;/i&gt; is for ranged ones.
      |You can also task them with &lt;i&gt;practicing&lt;/i&gt; a weapon - which will allow them to sharpen their melee or shooting skills - or &lt;i&gt;experimenting with an unknown weapon&lt;/i&gt; - which is &lt;b&gt;a very risky business!&lt;/b&gt; If sucessful, this will allow your colonists to equip a weapon that's more advanced than the current colony knowledge, but at a high risk of damaging the weapon in the process... or getting hurt themselves!
      |
      |For more details on how to play with this mod and how it works, check out the wiki on our GitHub page. The link is in the description.
      |
      |Enjoy!
      |
      |img:Passion|caption:&lt;b&gt;Please, consider supporting the making of this mod!&lt;/b&gt;
      |If you are able to contribute, you can buy me a coffee on &lt;i&gt;https://ko-fi.com/jptrrs&lt;/i&gt;, or follow the link above for our Patreon page, where you can also find &lt;b&gt;more mods&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;add-ons&lt;/b&gt; that aren't on Steam!
      |Many, many thanks!
    </content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="HumanResources.UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>HumanResources_1_1</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>1.1</assemblyVersion>
    <content>
      |&lt;b&gt;Weapons proficiency revision!&lt;/b&gt;
      |- &lt;i&gt;Clutter cleared.&lt;/i&gt;   I've changed the rules for displaying weapons on the proficiency list at the Tech tab. Artillery and common weapons (such as bottles) will now only show up when filtered for. Turret guns were excluded, since they can't really be equipped.
      |- &lt;i&gt;No more free bows and arrows.&lt;/i&gt;  Colonists no longer start knowing how to wield simple weapons that didn't require training from inferior tech levels. Instead...
      |- &lt;i&gt;Tech-enabled common weapons.&lt;/i&gt;  Now there is a middle-ground between training-required weapons and those simply known by anyone. These "easy" weapons will become available to your colonists as soon as their corresponding technology is added to your library, no training required. &lt;i&gt;All Artillery and mounted weapons&lt;/i&gt; will now follow that logic. If you know any modded weapons that also fit that bill, let me know and I might include them.
      |There were other unrelated bugfixes and improvements. Check the change notes on our Steam page for a complete list.
      |
      |img:Passion|caption:&lt;b&gt;Please, consider supporting the making of this mod!&lt;/b&gt;
      |If you are able to contribute, you can buy me a coffee on &lt;i&gt;https://ko-fi.com/jptrrs&lt;/i&gt;, or follow the link above for our Patreon page, where you can also find &lt;b&gt;more mods&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;add-ons&lt;/b&gt; that aren't on Steam!
      |Many, many thanks!
    </content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="HumanResources.UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>HumanResources_1_2</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>1.2</assemblyVersion>
    <content>
      |&lt;b&gt;Bridging the Gap revision!&lt;/b&gt;
      |- &lt;i&gt;Slaves tightened up.&lt;/i&gt;   The same knowledge restrictions that apply to your regular colonists will now also affect your slaves. They had too much of a slack!
      |- &lt;i&gt;Better feedback on Tech Levels and research costs.&lt;/i&gt;  Unlike vanilla, with &lt;i&gt;HR&lt;/i&gt; your faction's starting tech level doesn't affect your research costs. But the the Research Tree UI didn't get the memo. We've fixed this, so the techs' cost and tooltips are now accurate.
      |img:TLindicator
      |What &lt;b&gt;does&lt;/b&gt; affect your research is your researcher's personal tech level. To make that clearer, we've put this indicator on their &lt;i&gt;Tech&lt;/i&gt; tab to show where their expertise stands. Also, the cost for the individual techs displayed there will now be dynamically calculated, varying from pawn to pawn and according to the work they put in. Hover your mouse over that number to see a breakdown of those calculations.
      |On top of that, we've added and improved compatibility to a couple of mods. Check the change notes on our Steam page for a complete breakdown.
      |
      |img:Passion|caption:&lt;b&gt;Please, consider supporting the making of this mod!&lt;/b&gt;
      |If you are able to contribute, you can buy me a coffee on &lt;i&gt;https://ko-fi.com/jptrrs&lt;/i&gt;, or follow the link above for our Patreon page, where you can also find &lt;b&gt;more mods&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;add-ons&lt;/b&gt; that aren't on Steam!
      |Many, many thanks!
    </content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

  <!--<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="HumanResources.UpdateFeatureBase">
	<defName>HumanResources_0_1</defName>
	<assemblyVersion>0.1</assemblyVersion>
  <targetAudience>NewPlayers</targetAudience>
    <content>
      &lt;b&gt;You've been recruited to test this out!&lt;/b&gt;
      |This is a work in progress, and we're thrilled you are giving it a shot! Bear in mind you might encounter some errors and incompatibilities. If you do, please let me know. Don't forget to hit Ctrl+F12 to upload the error log and send me that link. I'm also open to any suggestions you might have, so please keep in touch!
      |
      |&lt;b&gt;Here's a quick guide to get you started:&lt;/b&gt;
      |img:TechButton
      |Check out the new tab for your colonists. It displays the sum of their knowledge, and that represents the limit of what they are able to build, repair, craft, grow and also the weapons they are able to equip. A starting knowledge set is generated for every pawn based on background, age and faction. From there, its your task to educate them!
      |
      |img:Study+Shelf
      |Build a &lt;i&gt;study desk&lt;/i&gt; and a &lt;i&gt;bookshelf&lt;/i&gt; as soon as you can. This allows your colonists to &lt;i&gt;document&lt;/i&gt; their knowledge into books and then &lt;i&gt;study&lt;/i&gt; books to acquire new knowledge (when assigned to &lt;i&gt;study&lt;/i&gt;).
      |
      |img:ResearchBenches
      |These are the new, more compact research benches. Their function hasn't changed, but you'll assign research projects individually to each colonist and what they learn will remain only in their heads until they can write a book on their discoveries. Only when that book is archived on a bookshelf you will really have unlocked that technology.
      |
      |img:Target+Dummy
      |When you discover new weapons, your colonists will need to train at these facilities in order to learn how to use them (for that, they must also be assigned to &lt;i&gt;study&lt;/i&gt;). The &lt;i&gt;training dummy&lt;/i&gt; is for meleee weapons and the &lt;i&gt;target stand&lt;/i&gt; is for ranged ones. You can also task them with &lt;i&gt;practicing&lt;/i&gt; a weapon. This will allow them to sharpen their melee or shooting skills!
      |
      |img:Quarantine|caption:&lt;b&gt;Please, consider supporting the making of this mod!&lt;/b&gt;
      This is being made as I try to mantain myself as isolated as possible during the COVID-19 crisis. Like many people around the world, my living has been impacted by the global efforts to contain the pandemic, and this is my effort to remain productive. If you are able to contribute, you can buy me a coffee on https://ko-fi.com/jptrrs, or follow the link above.
      Many, many thanks for your support!
    </content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
  
  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="HumanResources.UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>HumanResources_0_11</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>0.11</assemblyVersion>
    <content>
      &lt;b&gt;Friendly Update (IMPORTANT!)&lt;/b&gt;
      |The feedback you gave us on this first testing round has provided very valuable insights on how to improve &lt;i&gt;Human Resources&lt;/i&gt;. Beyond the usual fixes and compatibility patches, this update adresses some issues to try and make it more intuitive and give you the player better information. These are the main changes. If you're in the middle of a game you started before the update, there are some changes you should be aware of. (Also, in that case, if you get any errors, please try deleting any current bills on research and study benches.)
      |1. The &lt;i&gt;Learn&lt;/i&gt; work type has been renamed to &lt;b&gt;Study&lt;/b&gt;.
      |2. The &lt;i&gt;document technology&lt;/i&gt; task you assign your colonists to write books down now also belongs to the &lt;b&gt;study&lt;/b&gt; work type, since that's made at the &lt;i&gt;study desk&lt;/i&gt;. ;-)
      |3. It used to be possible for a pawn to learn a new weapon only if the corresponding technology book was already stored in one of your bookshelves. &lt;b&gt;Now, if the pawn already knows that technolgy personally, he or she will also be able to train with that weapon&lt;/b&gt;. To allow for this, the weapons list on the recipe window no longer hides the weapons your colony can't access. Therefore, keep in mind there will be weapons you can check but your pawns won't necessarily be able to learn.
      |4. The &lt;i&gt;Tech tab&lt;/i&gt; has gained some new capabilities. Check the new controls!|img:newButtons
      |5. The speed for the research and study tasks now scales with the difficulty level selected for your game, slowing down on higher levels (on top of the difficulty scaling the base game already applies to the research task). This means researching with &lt;i&gt;Human Resources&lt;/i&gt; will be even more difficult on higher difficulty levels. You can turn that off, if you wish, on the mod options menu.
      |Check the full change notes on our Steam page.
      |
      |&lt;b&gt;Please, consider supporting the making of this mod!&lt;/b&gt; If you are able to contribute, you can buy me a coffee on https://ko-fi.com/jptrrs, or follow the link above. Many, many thanks!
    </content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
  
  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="HumanResources.UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>HumanResources_0_16</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>0.16</assemblyVersion>
    <content>
      &lt;b&gt;Easy Homework Update (IMPORTANT!)&lt;/b&gt;
      |Following your feedback, we've made important changes to the way you select technologies for your colonists to study, document and research. The days of picking techs on the bills ingredient filter are over! Instead, now you do it...
      |A) &lt;b&gt;On the Tech tab itself&lt;/b&gt;, simply by clicking on the desired technology. 
      |img:HomeworkIndicator|caption:If the pawn knows it but its not on your library yet, it will be marked to be documented. If he doesn't know it but it's available, it will be marked for studying.
      |B) &lt;b&gt;On the main Research Tab&lt;/b&gt;, by clicking on the the desired tech and selecting the pawn on a pop-up menu. 
      |img:HomeworkOnTree|caption:This will set the techs to be researched or studied, depending on their availability. A picture of your colonist will be displayed on that tech, so it will be much easier to plan his path.
      |The game will automatically assign any other pre-requisites that might be necessary, so no more hassle trying to figure this out! By the way: now a pawn can forego learning a pre-requisite tech if he already knows its descendants. (No need to go all the way back to &lt;i&gt;Smithing&lt;/i&gt; in order to research &lt;i&gt;Machining&lt;/i&gt; if you're already an expert &lt;i&gt;Gunsmith&lt;/i&gt;!)
      |Those changes mean we don't need the bills on the Research Benches anymore. But they remain on the Study Desk, where you must still assign &lt;i&gt;study&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;documenting&lt;/i&gt; jobs.  
      |Check the full change notes on our Steam page.
      |&lt;b&gt;Please, consider supporting the making of this mod!&lt;/b&gt; If you are able to contribute, you can buy me a coffee on https://ko-fi.com/jptrrs, or follow the link above. Many, many thanks!
    </content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
  
  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="HumanResources.UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>HumanResources_0_19</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>0.19</assemblyVersion>
    <content>
      &lt;b&gt;"Don't try this at home"  Update&lt;/b&gt;
      |This time around we focused on what seemed to bother people the most about the mod: weapon training. The jobs at the &lt;i&gt;Target Stand&lt;/i&gt; and the &lt;i&gt;Training Dummy&lt;/i&gt; were re-worked and improved, among other changes. Here are the ones you might want to know about:
      |1. When training with a new weapon, &lt;b&gt;the pawns will no longer drop their current equipped one&lt;/b&gt;, keeping them on their inventory instead. When they are done, they'll drop the weapon they were training with and re-equip the one they were using before.
      |2. When learning a new ranged weapon, the pawns will become proficient in &lt;b&gt;all weapons&lt;/b&gt; unlocked by that technology at the same time. This should make it easier to keep up the pace in games with many weapon mods. If you feel you don't need the nerf, you can turn it off on the mod settings panel, where you can also apply that rule to melee weapons if you want to, as well.
      |3. You can now set up a bill for your pawns to &lt;b&gt;Experiment with an unknown weapon.&lt;/b&gt; This has the benefit of allowing them to learn how to use advanced weapons you can't yet fabricate. But since they will be literally playing with fire, &lt;b&gt;there's a good chance they will mess things up and end up injuring themselves or damaging (or even destroying) the weapon&lt;/b&gt;. The more advanced the thing, the more dangerous it is. Proceed at your own risk!
      |4. Practicing with weapons is now restricted to pawns equipped with the appropriate piece: ranged weapons to do it at the &lt;i&gt;Target Stand&lt;/i&gt; and melee weapons for practicing at the &lt;i&gt;Training Dummy&lt;/i&gt;. Also, we made it possible for your pawns to &lt;b&gt;do this just for fun&lt;/b&gt;, even if you don't set up a bill for it.
      |5. You can now choose, in the mod options panel, if you prefer single-use weapons, like &lt;i&gt;rocket lauchers&lt;/i&gt;, to also require training.
      |Apart from weapon training, we made a couple key changes to other areas:
      |6. After researching a new technology, &lt;b&gt;it will be automatically assigned for the pawn to document it&lt;/b&gt;. Provided there's a study desk with the corresponding bill set up, the pawns will proceed to write the corresponding book on their own.
      |7. The paws &lt;b&gt;will no longer write a book&lt;/b&gt; if there's no space on your library to hold it.
      |8. The capacity of &lt;i&gt;Book Shelves&lt;/i&gt; will now scale based on how many research projects were added by other mods, increasing proportionally to the technologies count. (This might mean their capacity was &lt;i&gt;reduced&lt;/i&gt; on games with few mods.) The limit of how many shelves can link to a single workstation was also raised, so you can now leverage the full power of the knowledge you accumulate.
      |9. The AI won't take into consideration the value of your library when determining the adequate threat levels anymore.
      |Check the full change notes on our Steam page.
      |&lt;b&gt;Please, consider supporting the making of this mod!&lt;/b&gt; If you are able to contribute, you can buy me a coffee on https://ko-fi.com/jptrrs, or follow the link above. Many, many thanks!
    </content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="HumanResources.UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>HumanResources_0_33</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>0.33</assemblyVersion>
    <content>
      &lt;b&gt;Information Age Update&lt;/b&gt;
      |These are the last big changes we're doing on this beta phase of &lt;i&gt;Human Resources&lt;/i&gt;. It's almost ready! Buckle up, they might impact your current game.
      |img:..\Textures\Things\Building\NetworkServer|caption:The new &lt;i&gt;Network Server&lt;/i&gt; is the bookshelf evolution, available with Microeletronics (and found on the Misc menu). It's able to store your whole library into one unit. And it doesn't matter where you place it, it's all accessible via wi-fi. Your own cloud! But in order to use it you'll also need...
      |img:..\Textures\Things\Building\NetworkTerminal_north|caption:The new &lt;i&gt;Network Terminal&lt;/i&gt;. This acts as a late-game study desk. It's slighlty faster, but also allows your colony to properly enter the digital age: you can scan your old books or write new ones and upload them directly to your network server, no physical copies needed! Of course, its speed is boosted by books on the cloud instead of the ones in shelves.
      |You're going to need this new data infrastucture in order to deal with a crucial change to the way books work:
      |img:..\Textures\Things\Item\drive|caption:From now on, technologies for the Space Age and beyond will only be found in the form of hard drives. And these can only be archived on network servers, via the terminal. Until you are able to build it, &lt;b&gt;it will be impossible for pawns with advanced knowledge to document what they know&lt;/b&gt;.
      |Other important changes:
      |1. Experimenting with unknown weapons on the Training Dummy and Target Stand will now require melee and shooting skills, respectively, instead of intellectual. Also, the test difficulty will take into account the pawn's own techlevel, instead of his faction's.
      |2. The recipe filters are re-enabled for all recipes, so if you want to limit what kind of knowledge your pawns will have access to, you can.
      |3. The Research Tree will now display a marker beside known techs to indicate whether they're stored in book or digital forms.
      |Full change notes on our Steam page. 
      |Enjoy!
      |img:Passion|caption:&lt;i&gt;Check out our Patreon page for more mods and add-ons that aren't on Steam!&lt;/i&gt; Follow the link above or go to https://www.patreon.com/jptrrs.
    </content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="HumanResources.UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>HumanResources_0_37</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>0.37</assemblyVersion>
    <content>
      &lt;b&gt;Coming of Age Update&lt;/b&gt;
      |This is a quick one:
      |img:..\Textures\UI\skills|caption:Check this cool new &lt;i&gt;Group by Skills&lt;/i&gt; button on the Tech tab!
      |Full change notes on our Steam page.
      |Enjoy!
      |
      |img:Passion|caption:&lt;i&gt;Check out our Patreon page for more mods and add-ons that aren't on Steam!&lt;/i&gt; Follow the link above or go to https://www.patreon.com/jptrrs.
    </content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>-->

</Defs>