<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>[JPT] Human Resources</name>
	<author>jptrrs</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>JPT.HumanResources</packageId>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</packageId>
      <displayName>HugsLib</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/818773962</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</li>
    <li>jelly.survivaltoolsreborn</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <incompatibleWith>
    <li>GHXX.TechAdvancing</li>
  </incompatibleWith>
  <description>
So, the brainiac in your colony spent a whole week locked up in his lab and discovered solar power. Great! Now, how exactly the builder figures out how to actually build the damn solar panels? Or else: you happened to find a sweet pulse charge rifle laying around, and you give it to your best shooter, who's been only using bow and arrow for his whole life. How the heck is he supposed to operate this space-age smart weapon?! How can you grow peaches if you never seen a peach tree before? Or craft a full armor set without knowing how to smith? What if your pawns had to actually learn their stuff before putting a new technology to use? 
This experimental mod with far-reaching consequences completely changes the way research plays out in the game. Technology is no longer some abstract concept, instead it is treated as knowledge to be individually learned from methodical research, by studying the proper books (yes, you get to build a library!) or, when it comes to weapons skills, to be acquired by arduous training (yes, you get to build a dojo!). Proper knowledge of what they're doing will be mandatory for your pawns to build and repair structures, follow recipes, grow crops and equip weapons. This will make you care a lot more for your colonists and give you a whole new perspective on recruiting. It will also raise new obstacles to developing your colony, making the game harder but also adding gameplay depth. We hope you're up to the challenge!

Warning #1: Not suited to be added mid-game. Please, start a new one.

Warning #2: This is a public test phase for an unifinished mod. Expect many issues and incompatibilities. We're counting on your collaboration to identify them and suggest improvements. Bear in mind the final product might be very different, and changes made during this process might break your game. If you're planning on starting a long-term playthrough (and we encourage you to do so, so we can test long-term effects), be prepared to make a local copy to avoid game-breaking updates.

Expertise
Books
Changed Research Benches
Weapon training



Yes, books! This is how humanity stores and shares knowledge. You can write them yourself, with the appropiate expertise, or buy them from specialized vendors. Your pawns will need to spend some time with them to expand their horizons. 



  
What if it was impossible to discover Microelectronics while sitting alone in a cabin in the woods? What if you actually had to learn it from someone who knows his stuff? This experimental mod with far-reaching consequences completely changes the way technology plays out in the game.
  </description>
	<url>https://steamcommunity.com/id/jptrrs/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100</url>
</ModMetaData>