<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>[JPT] Human Resources</name>
	<author>jptrrs</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>JPT.HumanResources</packageId>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</packageId>
      <displayName>HugsLib</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/818773962</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</li>
    <li>jelly.survivaltoolsreborn</li>
    <li>roolo.whatthehack</li>
    <li>bennington.medievalpatches</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <incompatibleWith>
    <li>GHXX.TechAdvancing</li>
    <li>fridgebaron.techsales</li>
    <li>fridgebaron.techblock</li>
    <li>doug.nojobauthors</li>
  </incompatibleWith>
  <description>
So, the brainiac in your colony spent a whole week locked up in his lab and discovered solar power. Great! Now, how exactly does the builder figures out how to actually build the damn solar panels? Or else: your hunter has been using only bow and arrow for his whole life, so how the heck is he going to operate the space-age pulse charger you just gave him? How can someone grow peaches if he's never seen a peach tree before? Craft a full armor set without knowing how to smith? What if your pawns had to actually learn their stuff before putting a new technology to use?
This experimental mod with far-reaching consequences completely changes the way research plays out in the game. No longer some abstract concept, technologies become actual knowledge your pawns need to learn from methodical research, by studying the proper books (yes, you get to build a library!) or, when it comes to weapons skills, to be acquired by arduous training (yes, you get to build a dojo!). Proper knowledge of what they're doing will be mandatory for them to build and repair structures, follow recipes, grow crops and equip weapons. This will make you care a lot more for your colonists and give you a whole new perspective on recruiting. It will also raise new obstacles to developing your colony, making the game harder while adding gameplay depth. We hope you're up for the challenge!
  </description>
	<url>https://steamcommunity.com/id/jptrrs/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100</url>
</ModMetaData>